{
  "kategoria1": [
    {
      "question": "Pytanie 1 kategoria 1",
      "answers": [
        "odpowiedz11",
        "odpowiedz12",
        "odpowiedz13",
        "odpowiedz14"
      ],
      "correct": "odpowiedz11"
    },
    {
      "question": "Pytanie 2 kategoria 1",
      "answers": [
        "odpowiedz21",
        "odpowiedz22",
        "odpowiedz23",
        "odpowiedz24"
      ],
      "correct": "odpowiedz21"
    },
    {
      "question": "Pytanie 3 kategoria 1",
      "answers": [
        "odpowiedz31",
        "odpowiedz32",
        "odpowiedz33",
        "odpowiedz34"
      ],
      "correct": "odpowiedz31"
    },
    {
      "question": "Pytanie 4 kategoria 1",
      "answers": [
        "odpowiedz41",
        "odpowiedz42",
        "odpowiedz43",
        "odpowiedz44"
      ],
      "correct": "odpowiedz41"
    },
    {
      "question": "Pytanie 5 kategoria 1",
      "answers": [
        "odpowiedz51",
        "odpowiedz52",
        "odpowiedz53",
        "odpowiedz54"
      ],
      "correct": "odpowiedz51"
    }
  ],"kategoria2": [
    {
      "question": "Pytanie 1 kategoria 2",
      "answers": [
        "odpowiedz11",
        "odpowiedz12",
        "odpowiedz13",
        "odpowiedz14"
      ],
      "correct": "odpowiedz11"
    },
    {
      "question": "Pytanie 2 kategoria 2",
      "answers": [
        "odpowiedz21",
        "odpowiedz22",
        "odpowiedz23",
        "odpowiedz24"
      ],
      "correct": "odpowiedz21"
    },
    {
      "question": "Pytanie 3 kategoria 2",
      "answers": [
        "odpowiedz31",
        "odpowiedz32",
        "odpowiedz33",
        "odpowiedz34"
      ],
      "correct": "odpowiedz31"
    },
    {
      "question": "Pytanie 4 kategoria 2",
      "answers": [
        "odpowiedz41",
        "odpowiedz42",
        "odpowiedz43",
        "odpowiedz44"
      ],
      "correct": "odpowiedz41"
    },
    {
      "question": "Pytanie 5 kategoria 2",
      "answers": [
        "odpowiedz51",
        "odpowiedz52",
        "odpowiedz53",
        "odpowiedz54"
      ],
      "correct": "odpowiedz51"
    },
    {
      "question": "Pytanie 6 kategoria 2",
      "answers": [
        "odpowiedz51",
        "odpowiedz52",
        "odpowiedz53",
        "odpowiedz54"
      ],
      "correct": "odpowiedz51"
    },
    {
      "question": "Pytanie 7 kategoria 2",
      "answers": [
        "odpowiedz71",
        "odpowiedz72",
        "odpowiedz73",
        "odpowiedz74"
      ],
      "correct": "odpowiedz71"
    }
  ]

}
